(Sheldon:)What's the only non-rectangular flag?
(Sheldon:)What animal appears most often on flags?
(Sheldon:)What animal appears second most often
on flags?
(Sheldon:)And more.
(Amy:)Sweet.
(Sheldon:)Why are you waving a white flag?
(Amy:)I'm surrendering to fun.
Now, today's episode of Fun with Flags
is not fun...
...but it is important.
Flags, you gotta know how to hold them...
...you gotta know how to fold them.
Let's start by identifying
the parts of our flag.
- This edge is the hoist and it's used to...
- Excuse me. Sorry, excuse me.
(Sheldon:)Cut.
(Sheldon:)Did you not see we are rolling?
(Leonard:)I'm having dinner with Penny.
I have to get out of here.
(Sheldon:)And I have flag knowledge
that I have to get out of here.